All your files have been encrypted! 
If you want to restore them, write us to the e-mail : ms.heisenberg@aol.com 
Write this ID in the title of your message DECRYPT-ID-a7777777-d777-7f77-77d7-7e77777d7777 number number In case of no answer in 48 hours write us to theese e-mails : ms.heisenberg@aol.com 

You have to pay for decryption in Bitcoins. 
The price depends on how fast you write to us. 
After payment we will send you the decryption tool that will decrypt all your files. 
Free decryption as guarantee Before paying you can send us up to 1 files for free decryption. 
The total size of files must be less than 2 Mb (non archived), and files should not contain valuable information. (databases,backups, large excel sheets, etc.) 
How to obtain Bitcoins The easiest way to buy bitcoins is LocalBitcoins site. You have to register, click 'Buy bitcoins', and select the seller by payment method and price. 
https://localbitcoins.com/buy_bitcoins 
Also you can find other places to buy Bitcoins and beg 

