ID:12345678
PC:[removed]
USER:[removed]
=======
IF YOU WANT TO GET ALL YOUR FILES BACK, PLEASE EMAIL ME AT:

epiclesis@protonmail.ch + kyklos@scryptmail.com + malakia@openmailbox.org

Send an email to all od these addresses, just in case, sometimes emails get lost.

Don't forget to check your spam/junk folder later, most likely my reply will end up there.

If you want to remain anonymous or if you aren't getting a reply, please try using bitmessage (bitmessage.org)
and use this address to contact me: BM-NAxZ29ouecw2Y7ibaXKus1vxDRDfheW6. This method will work 100%.

Encrypted files LOG: C:\Users\[removed]\Documents\12345678.log