NOT YOUR LANGUAGE? USE https://translate.google.com

What happened to your files ?
All of your files   protected by a strong encryption with RSA-2048.
More information about the encryption keys using RSA-2048 can be found here: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RSA_(cryptosystem)

How did this happen ?
!!! Specially for your PC was generated personal RSA-2048 KEY, both public and private.
!!! ALL YOUR FILES were encrypted with the public key, which has been transferred to your computer via the Internet.
!!! Decrypting of your files is only possible with the help of the private key and decrypt program , which is on our Secret Server 

What do I do ?
So, there are two ways you can choose: wait for a miracle and get your price doubled, or start send email now for more specific instructions! , and restore your data easy way.
If You have really valuable data, you better not waste your time, because there is no other way to get your files, except make a payment.

For more specific instructions:
Contact us by email only, send us an email along with your ID number and wait for further instructions. Our specialist will contact you within 24 hours. 
For you to be sure, that we can decrypt your files - you can send us a single encrypted file and we will send you back it in a decrypted form. This will be your guarantee. 

Please do not waste your time! You have 72 hours only! After that The Main Server will double your price!
So right now You have a chance to buy your individual private SoftWare with a low price!

E-MAIL1: rscl@dr.com
E-MAIL2: rscl@usa.com

YOUR_ID: 